kaaryah.com 2017-06-18

# Privacy Policy - KAARYAH

We ensure the privacy of all our members.  

**KAARYAH** is committed to protecting all the information you share with us. We follow stringent procedures to help protect the confidentiality, security, and integrity of data stored on our systems. Our Website encrypts your credit card number and other personal information using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to provide for the secure transmission of all data. Only those employees who need access to your information in order to perform their duties are allowed such access. Any employee who violates our privacy and/or security policies is subject to disciplinary action, including possible termination and civil and/or criminal prosecution.   

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTOOD, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR WEBSITE TERMS OF USE.  ****

**Enjoy Secure Shopping  
 **

We use encryption technology, digital certificates, secure commerce servers, and authentication to ensure that your personal information is secure online.  ****

**Your Registration or Account  
 **

**KAARYAH** keeps track of your information to offer you the best possible shopping experience. Before completing your purchase, we ask you for your name, phone number, email, billing and shipping addresses. This information, along with your payment method, is necessary to fulfill your order. This information may be disclosed to specific members of our staff and to select third parties (such as our credit card processor and shipping provider) involved in the completion of your transaction and delivery of your order. We may also need your email address or phone numbers to contact you if we have questions about your order. We or our associate companies may also use your email address to notify you about new services or special promotional programs, or send you offers or information if you have opted-in. Emails are sent only to  **KAARYAH** members who have chosen to receive them (opted-in) or who have made a purchase on our website. At any time, you can notify us that you wish to stop receiving these emails. Additionally, we keep a record of your past purchases, returns, and credits. We may also ask you for information regarding your personal preferences and demographics to help us better meet your needs.  ****

**Data Tracking Cookies  
 **

To facilitate and customize your experience with the Website, we store cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a User’s computer for record-keeping purposes which contains information about that User. We use cookies to save your time while using the Website, remind us who you are, and track and target User interests in order to provide a customized experience. Cookies also allow us to collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information from you, like which pages you visited and what links you clicked on. Use of this information helps us to create a more user-friendly experience for all visitors. In addition, we may use Third Party Advertising Companies to display advertisements on our Website. As part of their service, they may place separate cookies on your computer. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by our Website only and does not cover the use of cookies by any Advertiser. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you may be able to modify your browser settings to decline cookies. Please note that if you decline or delete these cookies, some parts of the Website may not work properly. ****

**Server Logs  
 **

In an effort to make our Website as effective and enjoyable as possible, the computers that operate it collect certain information each time you visit. We store these statistics in server logs. Once again, these statistics do not identify you personally, but provide us information regarding the type of user who is accessing our Website and certain browsing activities of that user. This data may include: the IP address of the user accessing our Website (i.e. the unique I.D. number of the user's computer), the type of browser (Internet Explorer, Firefox, etc.) and the operating system (Windows, Mac OS, etc.), the Website the user last visited before linking to our Website, how long the user accessed our Website in any given session, and the date and time of access. We may make use of this data at an aggregated level in order to understand how our Website is being used. We may share some of the aggregate findings (not the specific data) with advertisers, sponsors, investors, strategic partners, and others in order to help grow our business. ****

**Privacy Policies of Third Party Websites  
 **

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other websites that may be accessible through this Website have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. If you link to any such website, we urge you to review the respective website’s privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. ****

**The Opt-Out Practice  
 **

a) If you are no longer interested in receiving e-mail announcements and other marketing information from us, or you want us to remove any personal information that we have collected about you, you can opt-out anytime by sending an e-mail about your request to [info@KAARYAH.com](mailto:info@KAARYAH.com).  

b) We use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on this site. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our website, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other websites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. They do not know the name, phone number, address, email address, or any personally identifying information about the user.  

c) If you would like more information about this Opt-out practice and to know your choices about not having this anonymous information used by our third party service provider, please click http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. You can also read more about online marketing practices and the technologies that support them by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative’s website by clicking <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>. ****

**Changes in Policy  
 **

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised version in the “Privacy Policy” section of the Website. The revised Privacy Policy is effective immediately when posted on the Website. It is the responsibility of each User to review the Website and the Privacy Policy periodically to learn of any revisions to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website after the effectiveness of such revisions will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy. We stand behind the promises we make, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.  ****

**Contacting Us  
 **

Whether you are a new or loyal customer, marketer, publisher, media member or job seeker we would like to stay connected and want to hear from you!  

Please feel free to write to us at [customercare@KAARYAH.com  
 ](mailto:customercare@KAARYAH.com)
